If you want to buy a vehicle or a car, then first of all, he gets
its full insurance with death
balance because if there is
any damage to his hard earned money or the vehicle, then there is a
guarantee that he will
definitely get the clean chit and friends, he should get out which everyone else does
whether he is poor,
middle class or rich but friends, the most
important thing which people ignore is
health and in this they not only harm themselves but
also harm their family,
friends, in our country more than 70 percent of the
people are such who have never taken
health insurance because
they do not have any information about it, therefore
friends, today we will tell you
some important things related to health insurance mediclaim so that
such people have at least some information, by
this you
can assess your loss by getting your vehicles insured,
similarly you
can compensate for the hardships incurred in the eye hospital, today
we will know what is the festival and what are its
benefits, so let us know,
health insurance is very important in today's time,
otherwise, you saved money, you
worked very hard, did
not know what all and saved yourself an access mode  I have
saved 10-20 lakh rupees by working for 10 years, I have
saved it in the same way and if I get any disease then I will get
removed from any dealer group, for a strong
week, ten days, 15 days, how many people are getting Titli done
for my health,
this kind of evil eye has come,
New Delhi is Friday but the next people are like this, they are
heroes and directors only, they will join
and Shatrughan must have kept it for the name, so the
news is that
if you are related to waist singing then you do
not have to pay much premium,
margin money is wasted, you become
completely dependent on it, first you,
brother, your children, all the work is done, this is
obscene, this is medical, this is the cost, this has to be there,
what happens to such people
who have not got any tension cleaned
because now we can leave it,
this situation is in our hands, if
something happens to us then no one can do that if we
die, then what happens, the settings open will
end very quickly, what ends very quickly
and what happens, you will have to take a loan, you will have to
wash it, what does hiding that house mean
in your life  We will set it up by let's
understand how big the problem is and
how much it is that
you will never find such a pair in your life
when will the video come now the saint will keep on pouring water
either you will take it from the bank
see it from friends from here from here a however many
people there are and if you do not humbly you will
spoil this friendship the village has challenged
that eggs are not trustworthy how the box will turn upside down
you cannot do that in such a situation there are
some ways to save you and your family from the shortage of messages one of them
is health insurance
in a health insurance policy you pay a premium as per the company's instructions on
which day the fast is observed
and then you yourself become a cashless policy for the family
which will help in any case
if you have to be admitted tomorrow then the insurance company will bear all the expenses of hospital
expenses, medicines, operation, medical tests
etc.
in today's time due to the increasing cost of treatment
health insurance has become a necessity nowadays even the
smallest treatment costs lakhs of rupees
in hours friends today you
are healthy but there is no guarantee that you will not be sick tomorrow
friends nothing can be said about what will happen in
such a situation health
Insurance policy is for
painless, the insurance company
arranges cashless insurance for you, in such a facility the
customer does not have to pay the hospital bill, the
insurance company itself pays the hospital,
you also understand this
friends that if there is no tension of money then a
person recovers quickly and goes home soon, so when
people of health or wealth are asked the reason for accepting health insurance then
their answer is that it is a wasteful
expenditure, while some people also say
that they do not have such a big disease
that they need to take all this, but
friends the truth is that you
can pay ₹1000 every year for a shared bike, but
consider paying for health insurance of your family as a wasteful expenditure,
friends in foreign countries health
insurance is necessary and is mandatory for every person,
I never think that we will have to pay a
very high price for insurance, not very
less, you can get the insurance done, just
like you get your vehicles checked,
similarly you can get the repair of your house done,
but for example Jagriti takes a matupe, then it costs
five to six  Dude, the payment plan starts
disgustingly. If you
give even 1 lakh rupees to the company, then you can imagine for yourself
that in the next 10 years, no Muslim will fall
ill or there will be
no need for hospitals and medicines.
You also know this very well. Friends,
give this money even for a small treatment and they
easily pay it and go to sleep. But nowadays, there is
no limit on hospital expenses.
Even the poor get this notification and the
bill comes for lakhs of rupees. And the important thing is if I
think that if someone gets sick, then the medical plan is absolutely correct.
But if we take it, then this
plan does not take the claim immediately. It
starts after a few days. And if
someone has fallen very ill, like
he has started having
problems with everything and he
thinks that he should take the medical plan, then the
company refuses to give him the medical line. So
friends, dry insurance when you don't
drink well when you need you will not
enter insurance bread cheese balls. This is that
if any of Harold's is ill, then
we get relief from spending money.  It is available and
friends, the most important thing is peace of mind, there is
no price for this peace of mind.